<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Coloristance</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="new_game">Play Game</string>
    <string name="resume_game">Resume Game</string>
    <string name="music_pause">Sexy music pause</string>
    <string name="name_game">Coloristance</string>
    <string name="music_on">Sexy music on</string>
    <string name="door">Door</string>
    <string name="room">Room</string>
    <string name="test">Herro Herro ima little test-objectz ^^</string>
    <string name="key_desc">This is a colored key you can use to get access to a room with the same color</string>
    <string name="finished">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="play_next_level">Play Next Level</string>
    <string name="end_game">End Game</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="lost_game">Game Over! You ran out of time</string>
	<string name="back_pressed">Do you want to exit already?</string>
    <string name="time">your time is: </string>
    <string name="speaker">Speaker buttons</string>
    <string name="rules">Game Rules</string>
    <string name="maptext">You start in the white square to the left and finish the level in the white square on the right. The white dot represents your current position in the level. Move through the map as fast as you can! </string>
    <string name="roomtext">The color of the square is the room that you are currently in. The color of the doors correspond to the adjacent rooms, your inventory needs to contain a key with the same color as the door to open the door to the adjacent room. However, you do not need a white key to enter the last white room!! Click the speaker to pause the sexy music. The ticking number is the time you have left in the room before you lose.</string>
    <string name="roominvtext">Your inventory is below the room in this picture, see the red key in your inventory? You need it to move through to the red room! You can only carry three keys, so choose wisely. Click a key in your inventory to drop it in the room which gives space to a different key. You can not drop a key with the same color as a key that is already in that room. </string>
    <string name="takeabreaktext">If you want to take a break or quit playing, just press the backwards button and you can choose between three options: to continue playing, to replay the level you are currently at or to return to the main menu. If you choose to return to the main menu, then you can choose to resume the game and return to the same level and the same position as before you quit. Great right?</string>
    <string name="finishedleveltext">When you have completed the level, you can proceed to the next level. You will also see how long it took for you to complete the level. Try to finish as quickly as possible!</string>

</resources>
